<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<metadata>
    <name>Advanced Statistics</name>
    <directory>advanced_statistics</directory>
    <id>2494024575</id>
    <description>[h1]DESCRIPTION[/h1]

[b]Welcome to Advanced Statistics ![/b]

A modulable mod allowing you to track your stats all along your run (and compare it to your other runs !)

This mod is a little HUD that shows where the timer is, and uses a gradient of color to easily show your performance (red = bad, green = good)

To enable / disable the HUD, press [TAB]/[MENU]/[SELECT] for 1.5 seconds

For now these stats are tracked : 
  - Accuracy : (Hits / Tears shot) %
  - Level completion : (Rooms entered / Total rooms) %
  - KillStreak : Number of ennemies killed without being hit (Color depends on your average of your Maximum KillStreak)
  - RoomStreak : Number of rooms entered without being hit (Color depends on your average of  your Maximum RoomStreak) 
  - TimeStreak : Time spend without being hit (Color depends on your average of  your Maximum TimeStreak)
  - Hits taken : Number of hits taken (Color depends on your average of  Hits taken per level)	
  - Ennemy killed : Number of ennemy killed (Color depends on your average of  Ennemy killed per level)

[b]Tell me if you have any idea of additional stats, I can add them in future updates[/b]

You can choose to enable extra information globally. For each stat, You can choose individually to disable the extra information (basically the global stats)

You can also change the size of the GUD size (suggestion from solamon77)

There are multiple languages curently available :
  - English
  - English Detailed
  - French

If you want to help me translating to an other language (or correct my poor english), contact me.


[h1]HOW CAN I CHANGE THE SHOWN STATS ?[/h1]

The mod is totally modulable and is fully compatible with Mod Config Menu : https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1603631350
It's a simple menu that can help you with personalize the interface.

Otherwise, you can edit the configuration file (as_config.lua in the mod folder) to change the shown stats.
To avoid overflowing your screen, by default only two stats are printed on the base HUD and one when the timer is visible (and additional informations are hidden by default).
The stats by default are :
  - Accuracy, Hits taken (in the base HUD)
  - Level completion (when the timer is visible)


[h1]VERY IMPORTANT STUFF [/h1]

- When printing the map, the mod interface may override the in-game timer (or being shown not on top of the screen) due to internal modding issues.
If it occurs, hit [TAB]/[MENU]/[SELECT] for 10 seconds to solve the issue

- Accuracy only works on tears. For multi-hit tears (like piercing and ludivico), every hit will be taken in account. Familiar tears also count.

- This mod is not intended to be used in multiplayer, so you should disable it before. Otherwise, some stats may be broken

- The stats are common for all characters, so the max streaks may be broken by invulnerability items such as the mantle of the lost


[h1]TECHNICAL STUFF[/h1]


-- Average computation

Each run doesn't have the same weight. For example, finishing a run on the 4th floor will give your run a weight of 3 + X, where X is your level completion ratio.
This computation was chosen because dying during the 1st floor should not be as important as a full run.
And so, for the stats that are compared to the average, this average has been computed using mostly your best runs.


[h1]CREDITS[/h1]

A lot of my code (such as the way of setting config and language) is inspired from External Items Descriptions by WofSauge, so if you need an example for modding, I strongly advise you to look at this one (really good one mod, go spend your steams points there ;p):
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=836319872&amp;searchtext=external+items

Go look at the Modding of Isaac discord server, there is a lot of helpful stuff to learn making mods : https://discord.gg/JMaktQd
</description>
    <version>1.1</version>
    <visibility>Public</visibility>
    <tag id="Lua"/>
    <tag id="Graphics"/>
</metadata>
